[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] Meanwhile, as Gon
was summoning every last ounce
inside the west tower,
where Komugi had recently been.
[dramatic music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
FLASH X AND X START
I do not know.
[gasps]
[Menthuthuyoupi] I know,
and you're absolutely right.
I just… I want us to stay this way.
[Meruem] How curious.
It would seem that this feeling,
a side effect of my current condition.
and that means
you should be able to recover
all of the memories you need.
I believe that the selection
was to begin at 12:00?
[Shaiapouf] Yes, sire.
However, it can be moved up
if that is your wish.
[gasps]
What is it now?
[Shaiapouf] I haven't used my scales
on the humans
who are still on their way in.
and use them to hypnotize them.
What about you, Youpi?
[groans]
Let me think.
-Guess I'll look for Pitou.
-[gasps]
Pitou.
[dramatic music playing]
[Shaiapouf] Lord Meruem,
do you happen
to remember who Pitou is?
I do. One of my three
personal Royal Guards.
that I wouldn't
have remembered it before now.
Words can as well.
We cannot let him hear her name.
We must be very careful.
[Meruem] There it is again.
I'm counting on you, Pitou.
But what was it?
-Youpi.
-[Menthuthuyoupi] Sire?
Bring Pitou to me immediately.
We have things to discuss.
Right.
And what will you do, Lord Meruem?
I ask, because there are
still enemies around.
So there are.
I will go and search for Pitou myself
and hunt the stragglers in the process.
[Shaiapouf gasps] This is bad.
Uh, sire, that would be, uh…
It is merely for entertainment,
and I am certain that they have
useful information.
[Shaiapouf] Perhaps,
but we won't be at your side,
[dramatic music playing]
[Meruem] I want an honest answer, Pouf.
Give it.
[gasping]
In your personal opinion…
Sire, Lord Meruem…
[suspenseful music playing]
[narrator] The aura was overwhelming,
and as it spread,
it filled Knuckle and the others
who were still in hiding
with abject despair.
to handle something of this magnitude.
Hey, Meleoron, let's run for it!
Seriously?
You better believe it.
We'll just head back to the capital
under the cover of the crowd.
If they saw that, they'd understand.
They would run, too.
What if you and I were to team up?
[Knuckle] We could land
one attack on him, sure.
And if we got really lucky,
we could probably
even attach A.P.R., but…
do you really think we'd last long enough
for the King to go bankrupt?
Unless you've got the boss' lungs,
it ain't happening.
Besides, the situation's changed.
It's not as clear-cut as it was before.
we should have notified the association
so they could have
started working on plan B
instead of wasting all this time.
[grumbles]
Hurry.
[narrator] Revenge versus duty.
As they continued
to walk along in silence,
the difference in their motives
placed a growing distance between them.
[dramatic music playing]
before he could even think
to activate his power.
[gasps]
[Menthuthuyoupi] Where's the King?
There were two other Nen users there.
I could sense their aura
reacting to my En,
[Shaiapouf] One of them must be
carrying the unconscious Komugi.
That has to be where she went.
What do I do? What do I do?
[gasps]
It's just… If your purpose
is entertainment,
then shouldn't you take your time?
I get the sense…
you have a proposal for me.
[Shaiapouf] I do.
Would you be willing…
to engage in a game with us?
A game?
[high-pitched whine]
[dramatic music playing]
-[high-pitched whine]
-[dramatic music playing]
[Meruem] A game.
A game.
Youpi and I will both search for Pitou,
and in the meantime, you look
for the two remaining Nen users.
And we see who can
locate their target first, yes?
I would like to make
a request of you, Lord Meruem.
I ask that you wait here until I return.
It is painfully obvious
that the difference in power
between yourself
and the intruders is insurmountable.
In addition, we ask
for one further handicap.
"Further handicap"? What is it?
You will only be permitted
to use your En once more.
How does that sound, sire?
Mmm…
It's quite amusing.
[gasps]
I like this game. I will accept.
[Shaiapouf] Oh, thank you very much, sire.
Perfect. With this development,
I should have ample time
to kill that girl.
And as long as all of us are playing,
I will be granting each of you
a single wish.
[both gasp]
[both] Yes, sire.
This is an honor.
But, sire, what do you want
if you win the contest?
If I emerge victorious,
you will tell me all that you have been
hiding from me.
Is that understood?
[both gasp]
[suspenseful music playing]
-But--
-[Meruem] Silence.
Did you think that I would not
notice your guilt, your anxiety?
You truly feel I am so oblivious?
Were that not the case, I would have
beheaded you on the spot.
[whimpers]
I am certain you have your reasons.
That's only if I lose, understand?
Thank you, Lord Meruem.
I shall spread my scales at once.
I will not waste a moment's time.
If we lose this contest,
we will tell you everything.
This I swear on my very life.
[chuckles]
You treat this as more than
mere entertainment, don't you?
Once Pouf has spread his scales
and then returned to the palace,
I shall begin my hunt.
You find this acceptable?
[Shaiapouf] I do.
Then the victory will go
to whomever returns to this room
with their target first.
If Pitou should return while I'm gone,
you are to explain
were an octopus and a human being,
who seem to be carrying
some sort of burden.
No, victory is already assured.
The only question now is,
what should be done
about Pitou and the girl?
So where do you think Pitou ran off to?
It's all right.
Pitou should be back before long.
so you really aren't buying us any time.
Place your trust in me. I will not fail!
Hmm.
[dramatic music playing]
[Palm panting]
[Palm] Unbelievable. Such ferocious aura.
They were only knocked unconscious.
But where is Gon?
No, those are the only
two figures in my crystal ball.
That must be Gon.
Something must have happened
when I wasn't watching.
Where's Pitou?
In any case,
don't come back here, please.
Are they poisonous?
It would be better for me
if he'd stay near the King.
In any case,
he's on the other side of the palace.
I must get as far
from my previous location as I can.
After that wave of En,
I immediately used Wink Blue.
As soon as I did,
the King appeared next to Pouf,
carrying both Knuckle and Meleoron.
Only a few seconds had passed.
I'm sure of it.
I have to hurry and get even farther away
I have to go in there.
If I'm crossing the plain when he uses En,
I won't be able to escape.
If I'm deep underground,
perhaps his En won't be able to reach me.
But I'm not giving myself an escape route.
Should I stay outside
of the palace instead
What should I do?
Ikalgo!
I figured you'd be here.
Come on! Let's get inside! Hurry up!
Yes, but how--
Come on.
Isn't that why you came here?
If he uses his En again, we're finished.
[door whirring]
They're together now.
I don't know what happened to Pitou.
[Ikalgo] Hmm.
[dramatic music playing]
[Ikalgo] I see.
So Meleoron and Knuckle
were captured.
The King is on a whole other level.
[grunts]
They're alive, huh?
Probably so they can be traded.
We need to hide the girl
in Bizeff's room.
[Meruem] A game.
A game.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
Killua.
[Welfin] Don't you dare speak his name.
What do you know?
Just who do you think you are? Huh?